Why did they name it World War I? Did
they already know there were going to be
more?
>> Actually, the name First World War only
appeared in 1939 when the Second World
War started. Before then, people simply
referred to it as The Great War.
>> Wow, personally, I don't think there was
anything great about it at all.
>> Great doesn't necessarily mean good.
Great in this case refers to the scale
of the war.
>> I don't know. I think it's kind of
messed up that they called it that.
>> Well, what would you have called it
then?
>> Something negative, like maybe The Big
Bad War.
>> The Big Bad War?
Are you serious?
The Big Bad War makes it sound like a
fairy tale for children.
>> 4 billion people died, bro.
It doesn't get much bigger and badder
than that.
>> 40 million people died in World War I.
Where on earth did you get those numbers
from?
>> I made them up for dramatic effect.